https://empowerednetworks.com/privacy-policy/

Core Network Services
DNS, DHCP + IPAM (DDI)
Core Network Services
DNS, DHCP + IPAM (DDI)
Privacy Policy
Empowered Networks Inc. (“Empowered”) is committed to keeping all collected information confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Empowered are aware of our commitment to not only meeting, but exceeding privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement (“Agreement”) shall apply to Empowered and shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.empowerednetworks.com (“Site”) you are consenting to the following data collection procedures expressed within this Agreement.
Collection of Information
This Site passively and automatically collects various types of information through cookies, third party tracking technologies (HubSpot, Google Analytics) and server logs. Empowered may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system.
Please rest assured that this Site shall only collect personal identifying information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this Site to use personal identifying information only for the purpose for which it was requested, and any additional uses specifically provided on this Site.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements     of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in   which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected
Empowered may collect and may make use of personal identifying information to assist in the operation of our Site and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.empowerednetworks.com. Empowered may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Empowered may feel it necessary, from time to time, to contact you on behalf of other external business partners with regards to a potential new offer which may be of interest to you. If you consent, then at that time, personal identifying information, such as name, email address and/or telephone number, may be shared with the third party.
Empowered may find it beneficial to share specific data with our trusted partners for the purposes of statistical analysis, providing you with email and/or postal mail, delivering support, arranging deliveries, and/or operating our business. Those third parties shall be strictly prohibited from making use of your personal identifying information, other than to deliver those services which you requested, and as such, they are required to maintain the strictest of confidentiality with regards to all your information. We do not sell, lease, rent or give away your information.
Empowered may also deem it necessary to follow visitor and/or user activities while accessing our Site in an effort to glean what types of services and/or products are the most popular to customers or the general public.
Empowered may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply    with any process which may be served upon Empowered and/or our Site;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Empowered; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.empowerednetworks.com and/or the general public.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our Site have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To  discontinue or unsubscribe to our Site please send an email to info@empowerednetworks.com indicating that you wish to unsubscribe. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
For convenience, this Site contains links to third party websites. Empowered is not responsible for nor do we accept any liability for the information collection and disclosure practices of such third party websites. Empowered strongly encourages all users and/or visitors to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of all third party websites visited. This Agreement applies only to the information collected by the Site.
Children Under Age of 13
Empowered does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this Site.
Security
Empowered shall endeavor to take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of a user’s personal information under our control.
Information Retention
Personal identifiable information is retained as described in this Agreement and in accordance with our information retention policies. Empowered’s information retention periods are established considering privacy laws, the purpose for which the information was collected, legal and regulatory requirements to retain the information for minimum periods, limitation periods, and our business purposes.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Empowered reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy at any time. We will take reasonable steps to advise you of any changes to this Agreement, including posting those changes to the Site so that you are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Empowered decides to make use of any personally identifiable information, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. At that time, the user shall have the option to permit or disallow Empowered from using their information in this separate manner.
Site Cookies
As with most sites, this Site uses cookies and/or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer our sites and track users’ movements around our Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You may be able to control cookies using browser settings. For instance, some browsers are able to block or delete cookies, or to notify you before a cookie is set. If cookies are blocked, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site.  By continuing to use our Site without changing your browser settings, you consent to our use of cookies as described above.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this Site, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within this Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of the Site. In addition, your continued use of the Site following the posting of any updates or changes to this Agreement shall mean that you have read and are in acceptance of such changes. Empowered strongly recommends that you review this Agreement from time to time to obtain the current version.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Agreement, please contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: info@empowerednetworks.com
Telephone Number: 1.613.271.7970
Mailing Address:
Empowered Networks Inc.
750 Palladium Drive, Suite 102 Kanata, Ontario K2V 1C7
NoticeThis website or its third-party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in the cookie policy. If you want to know more or withdraw your consent to all or some of the cookies, please refer to the cookie policy.By closing this banner, scrolling this page, clicking a link or continuing to browse otherwise, you agree to the use of cookies. AcceptPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Integration
Data is at the center of nearly everything in the modern enterprise. From customers to products, from research to operations, from products to sales, from on-prem to cloud, your business survives and thrives on data. Combining different enterprise data in new and interesting ways, helps your business run optimally.
learn more
×
Professional Services
Empowered Professional Services deliver the solutions you require to operate and successfully implement your strategic goals. From our standard Foundational Services through to our Operational Services, we closely collaborate in all phases of our customer engagements as a seamless extension of your team.
learn more
×
Core Network Services
Efficient Core Network Services must be architected to enable high availability. They must support the robust capabilities required to effectively monitor, optimize and report on enterprise operations and performance. The combination of on-premises, virtual and cloud infrastructures as well as digital transformations like SD-WAN, multi-cloud and IOT have increased the importance of ensuring your Core Network Services are performing flawlessly.
learn more
×
Network Automation + Compliance
Empowered can help you automate routine tasks such as device discovery, configuration, provisioning and security operational tasks – getting things done in minutes instead of weeks.  Achieve and maintain compliance, respond to incidents in a timely fashion and deploy new applications faster.  Our solutions will help you easily inventory and visualize multiple topology layers and network constructs, such as VLANs, routes and virtual networks.
learn more
×
DNS Security
Digital transformation brings the tremendous benefit of increased connectivity, but unfortunately in lockstep with the rising adoption of SD-WAN, the cloud, and IOT comes the increased exposure to cyber threats. Empowered leverages DNS, the core network common denominator that underpins every digital business, to provide foundational security solutions that work with your existing security stack.  We help you detect threats quickly, stop them faster, and ensure peak performance of all your security investments.
learn more
×
Cloud Network Automation
Your business agility likely depends on your increasing use of private, hybrid, and multi-clouds.  Managing critical network services like DNS can be complex in this environment and may limit you from realizing the full potential of your cloud strategy. Empowered can help you automate your DNS approach across virtual and cloud platforms, allowing you to easily maintain consistent corporate policy. Our single-pane-of-glass approach gives you visibility across all network assets and allows you to effectively manage your network services at the speed of business.
learn more
×
Timing & Synchronization
Our team of highly skilled Experts has unparalleled expertise and a successful track record delivering high quality solutions to major service providers, enterprise customers, and companies that have unique timing and synchronization requirements. We have years of experience as specialists in timing and synchronization for all network technologies.
learn more
×
Ask an Expert
CLOSE
Privacy Policy Agreement
Empowered Networks Inc. (“Empowered”) is committed to keeping all collected information confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Empowered are aware of our commitment to not only meeting, but exceeding privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement (“Agreement”) shall apply to Empowered and shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.empowerednetworks.com (“Site”) you are consenting to the following data collection procedures expressed within this Agreement.
Collection of Information
This Site passively and automatically collects various types of information through cookies, third party tracking technologies (HubSpot, Google Analytics) and server logs. Empowered may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system.
Please rest assured that this Site shall only collect personal identifying information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this Site to use personal identifying information only for the purpose for which it was requested, and any additional uses specifically provided on this Site.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements     of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in   which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected
Empowered may collect and may make use of personal identifying information to assist in the operation of our Site and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.empowerednetworks.com. Empowered may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Empowered may feel it necessary, from time to time, to contact you on behalf of other external business partners with regards to a potential new offer which may be of interest to you. If you consent, then at that time, personal identifying information, such as name, email address and/or telephone number, may be shared with the third party.
Empowered may find it beneficial to share specific data with our trusted partners for the purposes of statistical analysis, providing you with email and/or postal mail, delivering support, arranging deliveries, and/or operating our business. Those third parties shall be strictly prohibited from making use of your personal identifying information, other than to deliver those services which you requested, and as such, they are required to maintain the strictest of confidentiality with regards to all your information. We do not sell, lease, rent or give away your information.
Empowered may also deem it necessary to follow visitor and/or user activities while accessing our Site in an effort to glean what types of services and/or products are the most popular to customers or the general public.
Empowered may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply    with any process which may be served upon Empowered and/or our Site;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Empowered; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.empowerednetworks.com and/or the general public.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our Site have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To  discontinue or unsubscribe to our Site please send an email to info@empowerednetworks.com indicating that you wish to unsubscribe. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
For convenience, this Site contains links to third party websites. Empowered is not responsible for nor do we accept any liability for the information collection and disclosure practices of such third party websites. Empowered strongly encourages all users and/or visitors to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of all third party websites visited. This Agreement applies only to the information collected by the Site.
Children Under Age of 13
Empowered does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this Site.
Security
Empowered shall endeavor to take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of a user’s personal information under our control.
Information Retention
Personal identifiable information is retained as described in this Agreement and in accordance with our information retention policies. Empowered’s information retention periods are established considering privacy laws, the purpose for which the information was collected, legal and regulatory requirements to retain the information for minimum periods, limitation periods, and our business purposes.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Empowered reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy at any time. We will take reasonable steps to advise you of any changes to this Agreement, including posting those changes to the Site so that you are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Empowered decides to make use of any personally identifiable information, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. At that time, the user shall have the option to permit or disallow Empowered from using their information in this separate manner.
Site Cookies
As with most sites, this Site uses cookies and/or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer our sites and track users’ movements around our Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You may be able to control cookies using browser settings. For instance, some browsers are able to block or delete cookies, or to notify you before a cookie is set. If cookies are blocked, you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site.  By continuing to use our Site without changing your browser settings, you consent to our use of cookies as described above.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this Site, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within this Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of the Site. In addition, your continued use of the Site following the posting of any updates or changes to this Agreement shall mean that you have read and are in acceptance of such changes. Empowered strongly recommends that you review this Agreement from time to time to obtain the current version.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Agreement, please contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: info@empowerednetworks.com
Telephone Number: 1.613.271.7970
Mailing Address:
Empowered Networks Inc.
750 Palladium Drive, Suite 102 Kanata, Ontario K2V 1C7
CLOSE
